smashitsusa.com 2012-09-20

# SmasHitsUSA.com

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

All personal information collected us on this site (for example, on contests/sweepstakes entry forms) will be utilized primarily for internal purposes and/or to enhance visitor enjoyment and experience. We may also use email addresses or other personally identifiable information to contact visitors who directly communicate with, For example, to notify visitors that they have won a contest/sweepstakes or to provide a requested email newsletter. Visitors may voluntarily subscribe to newsletters. We provide visitors with an option to unsubscribe from future email newsletters. Sometimes, personal information submitted by visitors may be used for marketing and promotional purposes relating to the Web site or other entertainment properties. We don't share any personally identifiable information provided by visitors with third parties, unless specified at time of collection. We bear no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information visitors may disclose on the bulletin boards, chat areas or other public forums on this Web site. We request that all visitors to the Web site that are under the age of 18 not disclose or provide any personal information on this Web site unless they provide written authorization to us from their parent or legal guardian. We reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. to learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

**CHOICE/OPT-OUT**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

**SECURITY**

We don't share any personally identifiable information provided by visitors with third parties, unless specified at time of collection. All information that is submitted on our site is stored securely and not shared with third parties. We take necessary and precautionary measures to secure our database.
